{"data":[{"question":"The Olympic Games ___ held every four years.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"have","d":"has","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Olympic Games are always taken in plural as there are several sporting events \n- Simple present (express the idea that an action is repeated or usual.) + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"All that can be used ___ worn out.","a":"are being","b":"has been","c":"have been","d":"had been","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (all that can be used) is singular \n- Present perfect","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Alice's teacher and friend ___ Mr. Lu.","a":"has","b":"are being","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"3","explain":"- Subject is singular \n- Simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"The police ___ the robbers everywhere when they suddenly appeared in a warehouse.","a":"are searching for","b":"is searching for","c":"were searching","d":"were searching for","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Subject (the police) is plural \n- Present continuous tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"The Gulliver's Travels ___ well known to the English world.","a":"were","b":"is","c":"been","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (The Gulliver's travels) is singular \n- Simple present tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Only less than 10 ___ of the population of this country ___ on hunting.","a":"percent, live","b":"percent, lives","c":"percents, lives","d":"percents, live","answer":"2","explain":"- Number + percent: 10 percent\u00a0\n- With words that indicate portions - percent, fraction, part, majority, some, all, none, remainder, and so forth - look at the noun in your of phrase (object of the preposition) to determine whether to use a singular or plural verb. If the object of the preposition is singular, use a singular verb. If the object of the preposition is plural, use a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"This kind of cookie ___ good while cookies of that kind ___ different.","a":"tastes, are","b":"taste, are","c":"smells, is","d":"smell, is","answer":"1","explain":"\n- First blank: subject (this kind of..) is singular \n- Second blank: subject (cookies..) is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Over 90 percent of the population of Mainland China ___ uneducated in 2000.","a":"is","b":"was","c":"will be","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"- With words that indicate portions - percent, fraction, part, majority, some, all, none, remainder, and so forth - look at the noun in your of phrase (object of the preposition) to determine whether to use a singular or plural verb. If the object of the preposition is singular, use a singular verb. If the object of the preposition is plural, use a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"There ___ a knife and fork on the table.","a":"seems to be","b":"seem to be","c":"are","d":"is seeming to be","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The words here and there have generally been labeled as adverbs even though they indicate place. In sentences beginning with here or there, the subject follows the verb. \n- Use a plural verb with two or more subjects when they are connected by and.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Kent has read a part of the book, the rest of which ___ more difficult.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"is read","d":"read","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (which = the book) is singular \n- Active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"}]}